britainfirst.org 2016-11-18

# Britain First – Taking our country back! | Privacy, refunds & unsubscribe policies

Britain First is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. We believe you have the right to privacy on the web. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. This policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

1\. What information do we collect?  
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;  
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any contribution you make to us;  
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us e.g. your email address and other personal information when you sign up;  
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters; and  
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.

2\. Do we use cookies?  
The Britain First website uses “cookies” to help personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize britainfirst.org pages, or register with britainfirst.org site or services, a cookie helps britainfirst.org to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same britainfirst.org web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the britainfirst.org features that you customized.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html. Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the britainfirst.org services or other web sites you visit.

3\. How will we use your personal data?  
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:  
(a) administer the website;  
(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;  
(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;  
(d) send statements and receipts to you, and collect payments from you;  
(e) send you general (non-marketing) communications;  
(f) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;  
(g) send you marketing communications e.g. email actions and marketing communications relating to britainfirst.org or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by email where you have specifically agreed to this, by email;  
(h) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; and  
(i) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not sell, rent or share your personal data with third party organisations.

4\. Donations  
We do not store your financial or credit/debit card details.

We have a refund policy in case you make a donation in error. If you contact us within 7 days of making the donation we will return it to you within 40 days without charge.

If we are unable to use your contribution for the purpose you specify, either because of oversubscription or for another unforeseen reason, it is our policy to use your contribution for campaign advertising, public relations, advocacy or organising activities related to the campaign that you donated to. When you make a donation not related to a specific campaign we will use our discretion to decide where those funds are allocated.

5\. Other disclosures

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we will disclose information about you only when required to do so by law.

6\. Security of your personal data  
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. You are responsible for keeping your user details confidential.

7\. Policy amendments  
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

8\. Your rights  
On receipt of proof of identity and a written request you may have a copy of any information that we hold about you. Please e-mail [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)

We will reply within forty days.

9\. Third party websites  
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

10\. Updating information  
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated by contacting us via [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)

11\. Unsubscribing  
You may unsubscribe from Britain First at any time by contacting [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)

12\. Contact  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)

Britain First is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. We believe you have the right to privacy on the web. This policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

### HOW TO GET A REFUND

If you desire a refund for a donation, membership or merchandise sale, please ring **0208 914 8212** (office hours) or email [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)

### CANCELLING YOUR MEMBERSHIP

If you wish to cancel your Britain First membership, please email [admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org).

All cancellations must be in writing.

Please note that all subscriptions for Britain First membership are subject to a minimum of _six_ monthly payments.

Should you chose to cancel your subscription before six monthly payments have been taken then the remaining balance due will be debited from the card details you have provided.

### REFUNDS TIMEFRAME

Most refunds can be made instantly, but we ask for a period of 3 working days to organise a refund.

### UN-SUBSCRIBE METHODS

Please use this section to un-subscribe from our email bulletin service.

If you want to un-subscribe, you have three options:

– **Ring  0208 914 8212**  
– **Email[admin@britainfirst.org](mailto:admin@britainfirst.org)**  
– **Click the “un-subscribe” link on your e-bulletin**

Please send all letters relating to privacy, refunds & unsubscribe policies to:

**Britain First, PO Box 119, Swanley, Kent, BR8 9DY**
